Nighttime and Idol
Yes, that's right.
I've sent you with Yasumoto-san.
What do you think? After presenting the three major elements...
I felt as if I had analyzed myself again.
It seems as if you have analyzed yourself once again.
Yes, but I think I talked about what I like.
I had a lot of fun talking about what I like.
I had a lot of fun and talked a lot.
I'm going to talk about beauty, music, and reading.
If you're a fan of Ms. Yasama, please have a look at her website and buy a copy of "Dare to Be Hated.
I'm going to buy the book "Courage to be Disliked".
I hope you'll read the same book as my guess.
I'd appreciate it.
And now...
Yasumoto-san.
I'd like to make an announcement about Seek Evisu Junior High School.
Yes, the TV anime currently airing...
The ending theme for the second season of Mashr.
Tokyo Zway" is now on sale!
We hope that everyone will listen to it while saying "way, way" and that Tokyo Zway is now on sale to rave reviews.
And the Tokyo Zway is also included in the new album Indigo Hour.
And our new album Indigo Hour, which includes Tokyo Zway, will be released on the 28th of February.
This album is about the shaky feelings of youth and the fragility and the sparkle of youth.
The album is a collection of songs that are full of the fragility and the sparkle of youth.
The album contains a lot of songs that are filled with the shakiness of youth, the fragility and the sparkle of youth.
I hope that you will enjoy it as much as I did.
I would be very happy if you could listen to it with a sense of youth in your heart.
I would be very happy if you could listen to it while feeling your youth.
And also
We also have a stage performance starring Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku!
Theater Shrimp
2024 My Sweet Little Lucky Day
will be screened at the Tokyo Sunshine Theatre from March 9th
at the Tokyo Sunshine Theatre from March 9th to 17th.
Theater Shrimps is a stage in which I play the lead role.
It's been a while since I've had the opportunity to perform in a classic play called Theatre Shrimp.
It's been a while since I've been back.
This will be our first play since we became a 10-member company.
I hope everyone enjoys the play with its rich individuality.
I'm not sure what the story will be about yet.
I don't know what the story will be yet.
Yes, but I'm sure it will be fun!
It's going to be fun.
I'm sure it will be full of laughter.
And what's more...
We are going on a nationwide tour from April to July!
It will be called "15th Anniversary Tour 2024 The Other Side of Indigo Hour
The title of the tour is "The Other Side of Indigo Hour",
The tour will be centered around the songs from Indigo Hour, which was released on February 28th.
This tour will be a great opportunity to hear many fun, stylish, and wonderful songs from Ebichu, so please come and see us!
We hope you will come and see us!
From April to July, right?
Yes, that's right.
It's going to be a long tour.
Do you get nervous on the first day?
Yes, I do.
Every year there are new challenges on the tour.
This time in particular, there are a lot of new types of songs on the album, even for Ebichu.
I think everyone is really into this album because it contains a lot of new types of songs.
I'm sure everyone is really excited about the first day of the tour.
I see. Well then, the last one is from Yakan-kun.
To commemorate the success of the national tour
I would like to let you know about a tea that brings out the weather.
I'd like to let you know.
Thank you very much.
This time, the tea is...
It's a blend of herbs to soothe your throat.
It's good.
Well, please enjoy the tea.
Bon appétit.
I feel your kindness, Mr. Yoru.
Thank you.
I put a lot of kindness into it.
Thank you very much.
And now... to the camera...
I'd like you to say one final word to the camera.
I'd like you to say goodbye.
Yes, ma'am.
From now on...
Keep an eye on Ebitu.
Bye, bye, bye.
This show is on
Mr. Market
Mr. Taso
Shota-san
Nobuhiko-san
Emi-san
Thank you very much
Sent courtesy of